Ganesh Sumurti Londhe

🔀 ganeshlondhe859@gmail.com 📞 9145496704 😲 Shiv colony ,near shiv mandir wakad, Pune

SUMMARY

1.2+ years of experience in Information Technology (IT) with an emphasis on Quality Assurance (QA) and Software Testing Life Cycle (STLC). This includes designing, developing, and implementing test plans, test cases, and test processes. These activities contribute to a fast problem-solving, significant cost reductions, and flawless audits.

EXPERIENCE

QA Automation Engineer

Qunatum TCS Inc August 2023 - Present

- Responsible for developing comprehensive test plans for various projects.
- Leveraged automation tools such as Playwright, Selenium, and Cypress to automate test cases, improving efficiency and reducing manual effort.
- Gained experience in using JMeter for performance testing and Postman for API testing.
- Familiarity with Playwright, a versatile browser automation tool.
- Utilized Azure DevOps as a project management tool to effectively manage project tasks and track progress.
- Successfully employed Azure DevOps for test management, ensuring organized test case management and seamless collaboration within the testing team.

Manual Software Tester

Quantum TCS Inc January 2022 - July 2022

- Developed comprehensive test scripts to ensure thorough testing of the software.
- Regular communication of project status to the team leader, providing valuable insights and updates.
- Created a well-defined test scenarios accompanied by detailed test cases to enhance testing efficiency.
- Prioritization of data integrity and implementation of robust measures to handle data accuracy and consistency.
- · Successfully conducted user acceptance testing to ensure that the software meets the expectations and requirements.

EDUCATION

B.E Mechanical Engineering, SVPMs College of Engineering, Malegaon, Baramati (Pune University) Percentage: 59.45% in 2016-2020

Higher Secondary, Tuljaram Chaturchand Arts, Science, & Commerce College, Baramati Percentage: 60.00% in

Sade High School S Percentage: 80.40% in 2014

PROJECTS

Elosity

Pharmaceutical Manufacturing - From August 2022 To till date.

- Created manual test cases in Azure DevOps, prioritizing comprehensive test coverage.
- Automated manual test cases using the Playwright Automation tool.
- Fixed failing tests in the nightly run pipeline.
- Conducted regression testing to validate the stability of the software after modifications.
- Created detailed bug reports and reported them to developers through Azure DevOps.

Mavrck

Inuencer Marketing - September 2022 - January 2023

- Created test cases in Jira Xray, ensuring comprehensive coverage of the testing process.
- Utilized Jira for creating bug reports, accurately documenting and tracking issues discovered during testing.
- Conducted performance testing using JMeter to assess the system's performance under different load conditions.
- Identification of areas for optimization based on the results of performance testing.

SKILLS

Languages: JavaScript, Java

Automation Tools: Cypress, PlayWright, Selenium, JMeter, and Postman

Databases: MySQL

CI Tools: Jenkins, GitLab CI/CD and GitHub Actions Management Tools: Git, Jira, Azure DevOps, TestRail

Methodologies: Agile, Waterfall and V-Model IDEs: Visual Studio Code, IntelliJ IDEA and Eclipse

Operating Systems: Windows, Mac